<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on (not)Unique experience</title>
    <link>https://fi5t.xyz/en/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on (not)Unique experience</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ru-ru</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 12:17:39 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fi5t.xyz/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Drozer on macOS Catalina</title>
      <link>https://fi5t.xyz/en/posts/drozer-on-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 12:17:39 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fi5t.xyz/en/posts/drozer-on-mac/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In general, I don&amp;rsquo;t use Drozer. And using this tool on macOS is unusual for me. If I do some &amp;ldquo;pentest things&amp;rdquo; I just take my Kali Linux with pre-installed Drozer and use it there. But the day has come, and I decided to install Drozer on my macOS. It was a real hell =)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spent a lot of time trying to make it work. Eventually, I had to rewrite a piece of class loader script&amp;hellip; A living hell! When everything started working right, I came up with a better way of installing Drozer on macOS and removed all this stuff . In fact, there are two good ways to do it. The Docker-way and the following one&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Context</title>
      <link>https://fi5t.xyz/en/posts/android-context/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fi5t.xyz/en/posts/android-context/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve come across an interesting article and want to share you my notes based on it. I made these notes as the mind map.
    Original article: Mastering Android context
XMind file: Download</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elemental Design Patterns (book). My review and notes.</title>
      <link>https://fi5t.xyz/en/posts/elemental-design-patterns-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fi5t.xyz/en/posts/elemental-design-patterns-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently, I read this book and want to share my thoughts about it with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you already know about GoF and their Design Patterns then the book will be a godsend for you. The author (and his team) did a great job to spread out GoF&amp;rsquo;s patterns into tiny, elemental patterns and to present the result to us. Why is it significant? It helps to understand the &amp;ldquo;big patterns&amp;rdquo; better and even build your own patterns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To tell the truth, the first half of the book seemed to me very boring. A lot of reasoning about &amp;ldquo;the meaning of life&amp;rdquo; and etc. I even wanted to stop reading it. Then I understood what this book is really about and read it from cover to cover.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>