<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>backend on (not)Unique experience</title>
    <link>https://fi5t.xyz/en/tags/backend/</link>
    <description>Recent content in backend on (not)Unique experience</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://fi5t.xyz/en/tags/backend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating mTLS reverse proxy with Ktor</title>
      <link>https://fi5t.xyz/en/posts/reverse-proxy-with-mtls-and-ktor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fi5t.xyz/en/posts/reverse-proxy-with-mtls-and-ktor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you like to integrate with external security systems, then you have probably come across such a thing&#xA;as &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mutual_authentication#mTLS&#34;&gt;Mutual TLS&lt;/a&gt; (also known as TLS mutual authentication or&#xA;mTLS). There is nothing particularly difficult in such integration. Except for two nuances:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Integration will have to be done in each service&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In each service you need to put client certificates for passing the mTLS handshake&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And if you can somehow live and put up with the first nuance, then the second already causes much more problems and&#xA;leads to sad faces of your security team. To make them happy again, and at the same time eliminate the need to write the&#xA;same code in each service, can be made by a smart &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Reverse_proxy&#34;&gt;reverse proxy&lt;/a&gt;, which&#xA;will take all the hardships and hardships handshake related and possibly some other additional logic. We will do this&#xA;farm on &lt;a href=&#34;https://ktor.io/&#34;&gt;Ktor&lt;/a&gt;, because why not;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To make them happy again, and at the same time get rid of the need to write the same code in each service, we will write&#xA;a smart &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Reverse_proxy&#34;&gt;reverse proxy&lt;/a&gt; which will take care of all hardships associated&#xA;with an mTLS handshake and other security logic. I will implement all these things with Ktor, because why not ;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
